sichermove.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy : Sichermove.com Real Estate Property In India

**Sichermove.com website is owned and operated by Menora Software (P) Ltd.  ** 

Our site maintains high degree of privacy as a matter of policy. Any person shall be bound by the Terms & Conditions of our Privacy Policy from the moment such person submits the registration form by accepting the Terms & Conditions stated in our website. By providing us with your information and visiting this web site, you accept and consent to the practices described in this privacy policy.

**Collection of personal information:**  

In the process of and in the course of rendering service to you, our site may collect personal information such as property details, e-mail address and names of the user etc. which includes but not limited to user specified password, telephone number, pin code etc.

While visiting our website we may place one or more cookies on your computer. We may track the IP address of a user’s computer and save information on your system/browser which could help to give you personalized information you want. We may log information from your computer including the existence of cookies your IP address and other information for the purpose of diagnosing problems, administer and track your usage of services. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings of your browser.

**How we use information:**

The personal information we obtain and collect is used to communicate with you and to provide services. We do not rent/sell personal information to third parties and will only share the information in the following circumstances:

Only if you have consented or directed as to share information, to obtain services from such providers or affiliate companies which performs services on or behalf to satisfy any requirements under law, to protect our rights, to present any concerns relating to fraud or security, or law enforcement authorities.

Information collected from this website may also be used to determine demographic and usage patterns. We may use your personal information for direct marketing or promotional activities. However you will be provided with an opportunity to decline to receive any information from us. The non-personal information we receive may be passed to third parties.

**Third party**

We use third party websites to advertise on our websites and those third parties use cookies to help measure the effectiveness of their advertisement. Our website may have links to other websites which may collect personal information. Our Privacy Policy does not extend to third parties websites.

**Notice**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice to you based on changes in the policy.

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please contact us at  _legal@sichermove.com_
